felt like every guy I know has a like a
great strip club story and I wanted one
so I actually spent 24 hours straight at
sapphire Las Vegas to get my story and
to beat salut you're driving me to
sapphire right now okay the best strip
club in Vegas yes it definitely is what
else can I expect in there a a whole
bunch of guys hitting on you thank you
because you're a beautiful person
beautiful girl hello our gentlemen's
club I'm disco nice to meet you I'm
gonna be spending 24 hours here in a row
in a row okay about 300 like the movie
like the movie why do people come here
it's an adult playground I said why do
people come here and you never mind why
do people ejaculate here people should
not be doing that here
now your name is cupcake yes
do you love cupcakes I don't but I think
my sweet sunshine face desserts cupcake
yeah I would be Froyo why because I love
frozen yogurt and you can't be frozen
yogurt coming to the main stage yeah hey
most of the strip clubs I go to or
attached to a sonic step up for me I'd
love to donate to your basketball team
let's just talk real talk how are you
gonna get the most money out of this guy
really pretend that I like him but I'm
not super interested in him yeah but you
do kind of like me like this
yeah um would you give him a lap down I
would love to okay it's great I've had
like a rough month a fan of my parents
are separating really are there cameras
in here
um probably know I was gonna masturbate
later I'm sleeping here tonight I'm a
man tonight you are a man today speaking
of men I have somewhere to show you
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe we'll get married guys can I talk
to you yeah my boyfriend has those socks
hi nice to meet you girlfriend
ha ha have you ever had a lap dance
before no I saw what you guys were doing
up there and it was it seems violent
violent just a girl it's time for bed so
I'm gonna get dressed I can't sleep it's
too loud
tell me feel me I love them it's alive
but like just you should just feel like
I do
[Music]
thanks for coming back I was just
sleeping in the parking lot I'm so sick
of beef you have the eyes of someone
who's in guantánamo right now I want to
go home so bad this place has been very
nice to me but I just I don't ever want
to be in a strip club again it's on my
shift tomorrow
[Applause]
please click here on my vagina where my
vagina would be in this push my puss
subscribe to my puss